articletrunk.com 2018-03-22

# ArticleTrunk.com - ArticleTrunk Privacy Policy | is an article directory for free online articles

ArticleTrunk.com - Website Privacy Policy 

Last Revised: April 12, 2011 

ArticleTrunk and its affiliates (collectively, Company or we) respect the privacy of the users of this Site (User or you) 

and are committed to protect the information of its Users. We believe that you have a right to know our practices regarding the 

information we may collect, use and disclose when you visit our website at the address [http://www.ArticleTrunk.com] (the Site or ArticleTrunnk). 

The guidelines contained herein apply to your visit or use of the Site.   

1\. Acceptance of the Policy   

PLEASE READ CAREFULLY: BY ACCESSING AND/OR USING THE SITE, YOU AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS SET FORTH IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY, 

INCLUDING TO THE COLLECTION AND PROCESSING OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION (AS DEFINED BELOW). IF YOU DISAGREE TO ANY TERM PROVIDED 

HEREIN, YOU MAY NOT USE THE SITE.   

2\. Which information we may collect on our Users?   

We collect two types of data and information:   

a. The first type of information is collected regardless of whether the User has registered the Site or is visiting the Site 

anonymously, and consists of non-identifiable and anonymous information (â€œNon-personal Informationâ€). 

To put it simply, we have no idea what is the identity of the User from which we have collected the Non-personal Information. 

Non-personal Information which is being gathered consists of technical information and behavioral information, as detailed below:   

Technical information:   

Type of operation system (e.g. Windows, Linux, etc.) 

Type of Browser (e.g. Explorer, Firefox, Chrome, Safari, etc.) 

Screen resolution (e.g. 800x600, 1024x768, etc.) 

Browser and keyboard language (e.g. English) 

IP Address. 

The domain name and host from which you access the Internet and the Internet address of the site from which you direct-linked to the Site. 

The date and time you access the Site and pages you visit. 

Any Similar technical information. 

Behavioral information:   

The clicks, mouse movements and similar information with regard to the User's session (e.g. the fact that User has chosen to click 

on a certain link or access a certain webpage). Please be advised that such information shall be deleted within approximately 

thirty (30) days after your visit to the Site.   

b. The other type of information is individually identifiable information ("Personal Information"). To put it simply, this 

information may identify an individual or is of a private and/or sensitive nature. Personal Information which is being gathered 

consists of any personal details provided voluntarily by the User (e.g. User's name, email address, author bio etc.) mainly by 

registration to the Site. We also treat any email you may send to us as Personal Information.   

For the sake of clarification, any Non-personal Information combined with Personal Information shall be regarded as Personal 

information.   

We will not collect any Personal Information from you without your approval. Among other things, we will not collect any chat or 

other correspondence between a User and any third-party.   
3\. How do we collect information on our Users?   

There are two main methods we use:   

a. We collect information while you access, browse, view or otherwise use the Site. In other words, when you access the Site we 

are aware of your usage of the Site, and may gather, collect and record the information relating to such usage. For example, when 

you connect to the Site, your computer tells us your IP address.   

b. We collect information which you provide us voluntarily. For example, when you wish to register to the Site, we may ask you to 

provide certain Personal Information which shall be kept on our servers. Each time you will be interested in providing information 

voluntarily we may ask you to consent to the collection and public display of such information.   

4\. What are the purposes of collecting the information?   

Non-personal Information is collected in order to:   

enhance the User's experience on the Site (e.g. by determining the screen resolutions). 

learn about the preferences of Users and general trends on our Site (e.g. understand which software is more popular than others). 

better understand the priorities and interests of our potential customers and partners in order to better suit their needs and 

increase the efficiency of our sales and marketing processes. 

administer the Site, help diagnose problems with our server, to gather broad demographic information. 

Personal Information is collected in order to:   

personalize your experience on the Site. 

provide you with certain information and services available only to registered Users. 

allow us to contact you with proposals and tailored information regarding events, offers, etc. 

identify you when conducting customer service operations (such as license purchase and generation, providing product feedback, 

etc.). 

other User Generated Content, voluntarily supplied by the User for the purpose of public use and display (e.g. public User Bio). 

5\. Sharing Personal Information with third parties   

We will share Personal Information only in the following cases: (a) to satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process, 

subpoena or governmental request; (b) to enforce these Privacy Policy or the Terms of Use, including investigation of potential 

violations thereof; (c) to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues; (d) to respond to claims 

that any content published on the Site violates any right of a third-party; (e) to respond to claims that unauthorized information 

(e.g. e-mail address, name, etc.) of a third-party has been posted on the Site by us without your consent; (f) to protect the 

rights, property, or personal safety of the Company, its Users or the general public; (g) when Company is undergoing any change in 

control, including by means of merger, acquisition or purchase of all or substantially all of the assets of Company; (h) pursuant 

to your approval, in order to supply certain services you have requested from Company; (i) to let our partners and affiliates 

serve you with commercials; or (j) with respect to articles, opinions, any other documentation supplied by you for the purpose of 

public use, in order to provide the services.   

6\. Deletion of Personal Information   

If for any reason you wish to delete your Personal Information, you should send an email via our Contact Us page, and we will make 

reasonable efforts to delete any such information pursuant to any applicable privacy laws.   

7\. Cookies & Local Storage   

When you visit the Site, Company may use industry-wide technologies such as "Cookies" (or similar technologies), which stores 

certain information on your computer ("Local Storage") and which will allow us to enable automatic sign-in to the Site, and make 

your browsing much more convenient and effortless. For example, and for your convenience, a Cookie can "autofill" information on 

forms on the Site, precluding the need for you to fill out the same information on our registration forms each time you want to 

access information that requires registration. However, cookies by themselves cannot be used to discover the identity of the user; 

It is easy to prohibit the Local Storage. Most browsers will allow you to erase cookies from your computer's hard drive, block 

acceptance of cookies, or receive a warning before a Cookie is stored.   

We also use certain third-party cookies. These are a different kind of cookies, which are stored on your computer by a third party 

site, rather than by the Company. This kind of cookie is updated each time you visit our Site, and also when you visit other 

website that uses similar cookies. Third-party cookies usually store only a Non-personal Information, such as the web pages you 

have visited, the duration of your browsing, etc.   

Specifically, Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on the Site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it 

to serve ads to users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART 

cookie by visiting the Google Ad And Content Network Privacy Policy.   

8\. Security   

We take a great care in maintaining the security of the Site and your information and in preventing unauthorized access to it 

through industry standard technologies and internal procedures. However, we do not guarantee that unauthorized access will never 

occur.   

Users who have registered to the Site agree to keep their password in strict confidence and not disclose such password to any 

third party.   

9\. Third Party Sites   

While using the Site you may encounter links to third party websites. Please be advised that such third party websites are 

independent sites, and we assume no responsibility or liability whatsoever with regard to privacy matters or any other legal 

matter with respect to such sites. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policies and the terms of use or service of such 

websites.   

10\. Changes to the Privacy Policy   

The terms of this Privacy Policy will govern the use of the Site and any information collected therein. Company reserves the right 

to change this policy at any time, so please re-visit this page frequently. In case of any material change, we will post a clear 

notice on the Site.   

Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective as of the stated "Last Updateâ€ and your continued use of the Site on or after the 

Last Update date will constitute acceptance of, and agreement to be bound by, those changes.   

11\. Who do I contact with the Privacy Policy?   

If you have any questions (or comments) concerning this Privacy Policy, you are most welcomed to send us an email via our Contact 

Us Page, available at [http://www.articletrunk.com/ContactAT.php], and we will make an effort to reply within a reasonable 

timeframe.
